techebizz.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Techebizz | Latest Trending News, Blogs, Analysis, Opinions, Reviews and Updates from Worldwide

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Ebizz Infotech collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://www.techebizz.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Ebizz Infotech.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except thatit may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### What type of Information we obtain and in it add

**Name**  
**Email Address**  
**Mailing Address**  
**Telephone Number(s)**  
**Blog or Website URL**  
**Photo**  
**Demographic Information (e.g., age, gender, interests, and preferences)**  
**Professional Title**  
**Company**  
**Industry**  
**Activities or Content Viewed on techebizz**  
**Information Collected Automatically**

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### Information Collected Automatically when you visit Techebizz

**Browser Information**  
**Operating System Information**  
**Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)**  
**IP Address**  
**Internet Service Provider**  
**Content Viewed**  
**Geographic Location**  
**Connection Speed**  
**Time of Visit**  
**Referring Site, Application, or Service**  
**Registration Time**

### How we use collected information

Techebizz collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

[The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order.

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Ebizz Infotech has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Techebizz does not control and is not responsible for the use of cookies by its third party partners or advertisers.

### In the cases mentioned below, Techebizz may disclose your information to third party vendors

**Service Providers**  
**Event Registration**  
**Web Hosts**  
**Third Party Websites**  
**URL/Referrer Header Information**  
**Advertisers and Analytics Services**  
**Law Enforcement/Legal Process**  
**Comments and Public Posts; Sharing on Third-Party Websites**  
**Change of Control**

### How to Contact Us

Techebizz  welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or its implementation. Any such questions or comments should be submitted via email to info@techebizz.com or directed to the address below. We will undertake reasonable efforts to resolve or address your concern.

### Corporate Office

Greencom Ebizzinfotech LLP  
5th Floor, Gandhi palace  
Near LIC Quarter, Timaliyawad  
Nanpura,Surat-395001, India  
Phone: 0261-2461010
